because i've heard all kind of crazy growing up yes like your nose always runs good because you
light-skinned light-skinned girls keep running noses i used to hear that all the time you know
what i mean so when i would tell people stuff like that i would say it in a way of oh i experienced
colorism too because these are things that happen to me and you know i had to fight and i had to do
this and i had to do that or what you know but what i didn't realize is that there's no way
impossible i'm experiencing colorism that's not what's going on colorism only goes in one direction
exactly so i'm experiencing bullying even if it's based on my complexion but i'm not experienced
colorism and i cannot go on these apps in front of these cameras saying like that because like
people already got that twisted and it's it's very simple but i mean i guess guess some guys
how i got the epiphany that's why it's like frustrating i google what colorism man the definition